<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<game>
	<title>Ganyang Setan Alas The Game</title>
	<release-date>September 2023 (Android), 2025 (PC)</release-date>
	<website>N/A</website>
	<press-can-request-copy>TRUE</press-can-request-copy>

	<platforms>
		<platform>
			<name>Steam PC</name>
			<link>https://store.steampowered.com/app/3351730/Ganyang_Setan_Alas_The_Game/</link>
		</platform>
		<platform>
			<name>ItchIo</name>
			<link>https://lodhongkrupukinteractive.itch.io/ganyang</link>
		</platform>
		<platform>
			<name>Google Play Store</name>
			<link>https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.setanalas.setanAlas</link>
		</platform>
	</platforms>
	
	<description>
	A single-player shooter adapted from the film Setan Alas!: The Draft by Yusron Fuadi and Anindita Suryarasmi. Set in a haunting Indonesian forest, this game plunges players into a thrilling fight for survival against relentless zombies, where resilience and agility are key.
	</description>
	
	<history>
	A group of four Software Engineering Technology students from the Vocational College of Universitas Gadjah Mada set out to create a game using Unreal Engine 5. Yusron Fuadi, the director of the award-winning film Setan Alas! The Draft, which was in its final phases of development, envisioned a game adaptation of his film during this period.

	The team successfully developed a prototype of Ganyang Setan Alas for Android in a two months. The prototype was revealed in August 2023 and sparked enthusiasm among the Vocational College community during internal expo events. The Android version was released on the Google Play Store in September 2023.

	Yusron Fuadi was motivated by this achievement to create a more immersive, realistic version of the game for the PC. Ganyang Setan Alas: The Game for PC was initiated in January 2024 when the project was expanded to include 11 students as the primary development team.

	The game garnered substantial attention during 2024, as it was featured at prominent expos such as INTI's GAMECOMM in Jakarta. Ganyang Setan Alas: The Game team intends to release a demo/early access version in December 2024, with the full release anticipated in early 2025.
	</history>

	<features>
		<feature>3 Primary firearms to defeat Zombies and bosses: Sniper, Shotgun, and Minigun.</feature>
		<feature>Be mindful of your choices! Each weapon has its own limitations, like the Minigun overheating after prolonged use.</feature>
		<feature>Utilize Detonable Claymore Bombs to eliminate groups of zombies in one massive blast.</feature>
		<feature>Turn the environment to your advantage! Shoot oil lamps to set zombies ablaze with fire.</feature>
		<feature>Stunning graphics with highly detailed models and shaders.</feature>
		<feature>Experience cinematic cutscenes that expand the lore of the Setan Alas universe, unveiling the next thrilling chapter.</feature>
	</features>
	
	<trailers>
		<trailer>
			<name>4K Trailer</name>
			<youtube>oBp6w5n_rBI&amp;ab_channel=AkasacaraFilm</youtube>
		</trailer>
	</trailers>
	
	<awards>
	</awards>
	
	<quotes>
	</quotes>
	
	<additionals>
		<additional>
			<title>Fandom Page</title>
			<description>Access it here</description>
			<link>https://ganyang-setan-alas-the-game.fandom.com/wiki/Ganyang_Setan_Alas!_-_The_Game_Wiki</link>
		</additional>
		<additional>
			<title>Release Blog Post</title>
			<description>The blog-post through which this game was released is available at</description>
			<link>http://vlambeer.com/bloglink</link>
		</additional>
	</additionals>
	
	<credits>
		<credit>
			<person>Yusron Fuadi</person>
			<website>https://akasacara.com/</website>
			<role>Director of Akasacara Film and LodhongKrupuk Interactive</role>
		</credit>
		<credit>
			<person>Andhika Rahmanu</person>
			<role>Game Designer</role>
		</credit>
		<credit>
			<person>Muhammad Ariq Srihadi</person>
			<role>Senior Programmer</role>
		</credit>
		<credit>
			<person>Muhammad Luthfi Azzahra Rammadhani</person>
			<role>Lead Programmer</role>
		</credit>
		<credit>
			<person>Rakhmad Hernan Syah</person>
			<role>User Interface Programmer</role>
		</credit>
		<credit>
			<person>Yahya Idris Abdurrahman</person>
			<role>Environment Programmer</role>
		</credit>
		<credit>
			<person>Anggito Wicaksono</person>
			<role>Programmer</role>
		</credit>
		<credit>
			<person>Herjati aji</person>
			<role>Programmer</role>
		</credit>
		<credit>
			<person>Wahyu Kemalajati</person>
			<role>Senior Artist</role>
		</credit>
		<credit>
			<person>Hafizh Favian Setiadhy Pratama</person>
			<role>Artist</role>
		</credit>
		<credit>
			<person>Christophorus Ardhito Haryo Dwinanda</person>
			<role>Environment, Animation Artist</role>
		</credit>
		<credit>
			<person>Muhammad Naufal Rosyad</person>
			<role>Technical Artist</role>
		</credit>
		<credit>
			<person>Rayendra Arya Daneswara</person>
			<role>Lead Artist</role>
		</credit>
		<credit>
			<person>Muhammad Mada Ibrahim</person>
			<role>Model Artist</role>
		</credit>
	</credits>
</game>